All those words of pride, courage, and even hope
Are all so half-baked and hollow
But even so, I thought, I want to protect people's smiles
And in that moment, I became a hero
Together, we share all our joy as the love spreads around
Tomorrow we won't be alone as we stand hand-in-hand
Our destiny is dazzling bright
Along the path I walked down, you were always right by my side
At the crossroads of emotions, where countless feelings meet
And now they all join together—a correlation diagram under the sky
Even in the deepest darkness, so long as the stars shine bright,
They'll light up any sorrows that we might have
And even if people are weak alone, so long as they look up at the sky,
It'll serve as proof that we're all connected together
As we walk up this hill and pass through the promised arch
The sea breeze will gently kiss you on the cheek
Our destiny is dazzling bright
In the scene most precious to me, you were always right by my side
That's something irreplaceable to me; now tears run down my smiling face
Let's head into a future unknown—a correlation diagram held up by the sky
Along the path I walked down, you were always right by my side
At the crossroads of emotions, where countless feelings meet
And now they all join together—a correlation diagram under the sky