The light within our reach felt like it'd go out upon touch
What pushed you through your doubts and hesitation
Were all the scattered fragments here and there
Which, once gathered and pieced together
Tell a story connecting past and future
The end leads into the beginning; the start continues into the dream
Because the glimmers of light will expand out for all eternity
The latest story finally begins, full of memories that will never fade away
'Cause they hold our precious feelings we want to hold onto forever more
And if the unseen truth is the only light shining down on our world
Then there's no turning back anymore
We're heading for the other side
Toward our promised tomorrow